♪ 我的站到了 ♪
♪ This is my stop ♪
♪ 得下车了 ♪
♪ Got to get off ♪
♪ 还敢更挤嘛 ♪
♪ I might go pop ♪
借过
Excuse me
♪ 原谅我这么直 ♪
♪ I've got to be direct ♪
♪ 如冒犯请指教 ♪
♪ If I'm off, please correct ♪
♪ 你挡着我道了 ♪
♪ You're standing on my neck ♪
拽妹Daria
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
——·旗木译制·——
我们可以给全班做纸杯蛋糕
We can bake cupcakes for the whole class
在那一天脑补你人缘很好
and pretend you're really popular for the day.
有小木马骑吗?
Will there be pony rides?
你有什么高见吗?
Do you have any ideas?
我就是不想庆祝什么生日
I just don't feel like celebrating my birthday.
完全是以刺激经济为目的的伪造节日
It's a totally artificial holiday created to stimulate the economy.
生日应该是祝福贺卡还没攻占的节日高地吧?
Aren't birthdays the one holiday the greeting card industry didn't make up?
这是他们迷惑你的说法
That's what they want you to believe.
好啦好啦 不办派对 不送礼物
Okay, okay. No party and no present.
谁说别送礼物了?
Who said no present?
披萨真美味 亲爱的
Great pizza, honey.
解决呼吸道哽塞的急救法
天 Daria Helen 海姆利克急救
Oh, my gosh! Daria! Helen! Heimlich!
放松 老爸 只是被奶酪烫到了
Relax, Dad. It's just cheese burn.
会哭的孩子有奶吃呀 Daria
You're such a pain wimp, Daria.
话说 老爸 你应该多买无奶酪披萨才对
You know, Dad, you really should get cheese-less pizza anyway.
那种更健康
It's much healthier.
无奶酪披萨? 好赞的点子啊
Cheese-less pizza? What a great idea!
嘿嘿 给我吃了呗?
Hey, hey, can I have that?
这是什么? 谁打开的?
What's this? And who opened it?
甭担心 这事儿没戏
Don't worry. It's not going to happen.
母女同台校园时装秀
A mother-daughter fashion show at school?
为了筹款?
To raise money?
...和筹觉悟
And consciousness.
好赞的点子啊
What a great idea!
时尚俱乐部已经召开紧急会议了
The Fashion Club has already scheduled an emergency meeting.
我们会拦着这事的
We'll put a stop to it.
因为不想让一群业余票友乱了你们的猫步?
Don't want a bunch of smelly amateurs stinking up your catwalks?
正解 Daria
Right, Daria.
要保持高端大气的形象 哪还能顾上拉一个时尚庸民啊?
You can't just mix with fashion civilians when you have an image to uphold.
还真是解脱
Well, that's a relief.
我是说 谁愿意四处瞎招摇 就为炫几件怪衣服啊?
I mean, who wants to parade around showing off some ridiculous outfit.
跟我妈肯定不愿意
With your mother.
喂?
Hello?
喂 能让您女儿接下电话么?
Hello. Um, can I please speak to your daughter?
稍等 Quinn 亲爱的 找你的
Just a sec... Quinn, honey, it's for you.
谁啊 老爸?
Who is it, Daddy?
没报名字
Didn't catch his name.
但愿不是Adam
I hope it's not Adam.
我本来打算把他拒了 和Simon玩的
I was going to cancel on him to go out with Simon,
但后来Todd电我 我又犹豫了
but then Todd called so I'm not sure,
如果是Bryce 没准我会跟他出去
but if it's Bryce, maybe I'll go out with him instead
然后拒掉Simon 反正他压根也没再问过
and cancel on Simon anyway since he hasn't even asked yet.
拉丁女战神
玛西亚 玛西亚 玛西亚
Marcia, Marcia, Marcia.
喂?
Hello?
你谁啊?
Who's this?
你打给我的好吧 你谁啊?
You called me, duh. Who's this?
我没打给你
I didn't call you.
那先失陪了
Well, excuse me.
好像是个搞推销的
I think he's selling something.
让他省了吧 妈
Tell him off, mom.
喂? 您不觉得这点儿还来安利有点扰民了吗?
Hello? Don't you think it's a little late to be soliciting people?
抱歉 七点还不算晚吧 不过...
Uh, sorry. I didn't think 7:00 was late, but,
Daria已经睡了吗?
is Daria in bed already?
Daria? 你谁啊?
Daria? Who are you?
我是Trent Jane的哥哥
Um, this is Trent. Jane's brother.
Daria 是Trent Jane哥哥
Daria, it's Trent. Jane's brother.
Trent Jane哥哥? 找我?
Trent, Jane's brother? For me?
是啊 不过他听起来有点迟疑
Yes, but he does sound a little confused.
是Daria 对吧?
This is Daria, right?
稍等 我得换个听筒
Hold on, I need to switch phones.
我上楼接了 好吧?
I'll take it upstairs, okay?
你们可以挂了 我接到了 挂了吧
You can hang up now! I got it! Hang up!
听筒在你手呢 丫头
You have the phone, kiddo!
好吧 知道了 我自己挂好了
Okay, thanks, I'll hang up myself, then.
嗨 Trent 不好意思久等了
Hi, Trent. Sorry about that.
Trent?
Trent? Trent
Trent? Trent!
嘿 Daria
Hey, Daria.
嗨 有什么事吗?
Uh, hi. What's up?
Trent? 你睡着了?
Trent? Are you awake?
我... 想问你点事
I, uh, need to ask you something.
我?
Me?
对 你
Yeah, you.
那...
So...
那... 你想问我点事?
So... you wanted to ask me something?
对 对 没错
Right. Right, and, uh, yeah.
听起来很完美 回头见 拜
That sounds excellent. See you then. Bye.
谁啊?
Who was that?
什么?
What?
你刚跟谁打电话呢?
Who were you just speaking to?
关你毛事
What's it to you?
你样子怪怪的 还不够?
You're acting really weird, that's all.
比我平时要怪嘛?
I'm acting weirder than usual?
别跟我玩文字游戏 小伙儿
None of your trick questions, young man.
你动作很诡异
You're behaving strangely.
你才诡异
You're the strange one.
- 你诡异 - 你
- You are. - You.
你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
你谁? 老妈?
Who are you? Mom?
不是 老妈才不会问你去哪儿
No, Mom would never ask where you're going.
那就对了
Exactly.
重... 拨
Rrrre-dial.
喂? Trent? 喂 有人吗?
Hello? Trent? Hello? Anyone there?
Trent 是你吗?
Trent, is that you?
Daria
Daria!
Daria 楼下的一家之主们...
Daria, the downstairs members of the household...
想把无线听筒拿下去 谢谢
.would like the cordless phone back now, please.
怎么了 Quinn?
What is it, Quinn?
没什么
Nothing.
跟我们说说嘛 宝贝儿
You can tell us, sweetie.
叹什么气呢?
What's got you blue?
就是... 我在T台上好美好美啊
It's just... I'd look so good on a runway.
他把肾脏捐献给她 她把心交给了他
He gave her his kidney. She gave him her heart.
《呕心小世界》继续播出: 浪漫移植
Transplants and romance when Sick, Sad World continues.
Daria?
怎么了 Trent?
Yes, Trent?
想听听我为你... 写的歌吗?
Want to hear this song I wrote... for you?
你为我写了歌?
You wrote me a song?
你是我的灵感源泉好吧
You're my muse, you know.
真的?
Really?
这首名叫《自我蒙蔽的小笨妞...
It's called "Silly, Little Self-Deluded Girl.
为什么我这样的酷男会写一首关于你的歌?》
Why Would a Cool Guy Like Me Ever Write a Song About You?"
喂? 嗨 Sandi
Hello? Oh, hi, Sandi.
真的? 听起来很萌 会很萌吧
Really? That sounds cute, I guess that's cute.
没错 肯定很萌的
Yes, definitely cute.
是啊 应该会很萌 但... 我再考虑考虑
Yeah, that would be cute, but... I'll think about it.
好 拜
Okay. Bye.
囧Sandi 她妈妈死活非要上时装秀
Poor Sandi. Her mom insists on being in the fashion show.
肯定得 她这个人极端自恋 你不觉得吗?
She would. She's awfully full of herself, don't you think?
反正我们比她们萌
We're cuter than them.
自欺欺人
Cuter than they.
绝对的事
Damn right.
Linda很有魅力的
Linda is very attractive.
你肯定比Sandi的妈妈更萌的 老妈
You're definitely cuter than Sandi's mom, Mom.
傻话
This is silly.
如果Sandi都能参赛 那猪也可以参赛了
If Sandi can be in it then everyone should be allowed to be in it.
我是时尚俱乐部副主席 我们非赢不可
I'm vice president of the Fashion Club. We have to win.
可这不是一场比赛哦
But it's not a competitive event.
会是的
Oh, it will be.
嘿
Hey.
Quinn 你男伴来咯
Quinn! Your date is here!
其实我...
Actually, I'm...
天啊 老爸 开什么玩笑?
God, Dad, are you kidding?
哎哟 抱歉 年轻人 你知道女孩子就这样
Gee, I'm sorry, young man, but you know how girls can be.
给她一点时间就好了 孩子 给她点时间
Just give her some time, son. Give her some time.
Daria在家吗?
Is Daria home?
Daria?! 你谁啊?
Daria?! Who are you?
所以你是来找Daria的
So, you're here to see Daria.
是
Yeah.
Daria这丫头有点特别 对不对?
Daria is a very special girl, isn't she?
是啊
Uh, sure.
你多大 Trent?
How old are you, Trent?
啥?
What?
上学呢吗? 有工作吗?
Are you in school? Do you have a job?
生活可不能吃了上顿没下顿 你搞清楚
Life isn't just one free handout after another, you know.
你耳朵上有几个耳环啊?
How many earrings in that ear?
Daria提过你有个乐队什么的
Daria has mentioned that you have some sort of band.
七彩玄
Mystik Spiral.
不过我们在想改名字的事了
But we're thinking of changing the name.
妈 爸
Um, Mom, Dad.
Quinn在厨房里打电话要预定一辆敞篷车
Quinn's on the phone in the kitchen ordering a convertible.
我的天呐
Oh, my God!
我之前不是有意要挂你电话的
I didn't mean to hang up on you before.
Janey当时走过来 我不知道怎么说好了
Janey walked in and I couldn't think of what to say.
没事的
Oh. That's okay.
Daria 我...
Daria, I...
嗯?
Yes...?
我想让你帮我给Jane选礼物
I want you to help me pick out a birthday present for Jane.
每年我送她的都是美术工具
Every year I end up getting her art supplies.
你能帮我创新一下吗?
Can you help me out?
为Jane在所不惜
Anything for Jane.
谢了 Daria
Thanks, Daria.
明早我过来接你
I'll pick you up tomorrow morning.
也别太早 午餐前或者... 午餐后吧
Not too early, sometime before lunch... or after.
没问题
Um, okay.
或者更牛X 我们干脆不吃算了
Or better yet, why don't we leave it loose?
不要吃啊
Don't do it!
Quinn 你诈什么尸啊?
Quinn, what is the matter with you?
意大利语
咖啡 咖啡因: 黑眼圈 明白?
Coffee, caffeine: dark circles, capisce?
时装秀哦 老妈 别给自己设障
Fashion show, mom. Don't handicap yourself.
Quinn 我得喝咖啡
Quinn, I need my coffee.
"某母嗜咖成瘾 失利时装秀
"Woman Loses Fashion Show Due to Pathetic Addiction.
其女遭受牵连 受辱一生"
Daughter Shamed For Life."
走啦 Spa馆马上就要开门了
Come on, the spa is about to open anyway.
Daria? 最后再问一次要不要加入我们母女同台秀哦
Daria? Last chance to join us for a mother-daughter day of beauty.
非常放松身心哟
It's very relaxing.
从痛苦中昏过去以后吧?
Once you pass out from the pain.
谁啊? 我今天没约会啊
Who's that? I don't have a date now.
是找我的好吧
I think it's for me.
几小时前我还没想到你这点儿来
I wasn't expecting you for a couple of hours.
我刚排练回来
I came straight from rehearsal.
晚排练 还是早排练来着 随便了
We ran late, or early... whatever.
话说我们去哪?
So, where should we go?
我想了...
Um, I was thinking...
不要美术工具 昨晚我们就否决了
No art supplies. We decided already.
也不想送她CD
Don't want to get her a CD.
另外我也不想进书店半步
And I can't set foot in a bookstore.
别问我为什么 Daria
Don't ask me why Daria.
我不想聊这个
I just don't want to talk about it.
说你想到什么了吧
So, what are your ideas?
毛绒小兔子?
A fuzzy little bunny?
我们去戴格大道吧
Let's just go to Dega Street.
我们肯定能在那儿找到礼物的
I'm sure we'll find something there.
我在想我们两个都穿窄管裤
I was thinking we could both wear cigarette trousers,
我上身穿露背装 你上身穿高领紧身装
and I'll wear a halter top and you could wear more the nehru jacket thing.
还有记住 老妈 萌不是一种表象
And remember, Mom, cute is not a look,
不是一种态度 而是一种气质
it's not an attitude, it's a way of being.
这姑娘是个小话唠呀 有没有?
She's a little miss chatterbox, isn't she?
我们在训练啦 她会做我的妈妈
We're in training. She's going to be my mother
我会做她的女儿 去参加时装秀
and I'm going to be her daughter in a fashion show.
当然她就是我亲妈
Actually, she is my mother
我就是她亲闺女啦 老妈?
and I'm her daughter in real life, too. Mom?
怎么啦?
What?
嘿 Daria 你觉得怎么样?
Hey, Daria, what do you think?
这更像是送你的礼物 不像送Jane的
Um, wouldn't that be more for you than for Jane?
说得有道理
That's a really good point.
还没见Jane穿过扎染的衣服
I just don't see Jane in tie-dye.
那件你穿着肯定漂亮
You'd look good in that.
谢谢
Um, oh... thanks.
人体穿孔? Jane吗?
Body piercing? Jane?
你从来不想玩穿孔吗?
Haven't you always wanted to get pierced?
不想 为了某种亚文化审美符号
No. It just seems too much like getting tortured
那样折磨自己有点过头了
for the sake of some subculture's notion of beauty.
现在上热风机
Now, the dryers.
我们会在您头部吹上20分钟热风 直到您忍不了为止
We'll blast heat on your heads for 20 minutes or until you can't take it anymore.
你们在我头上围一圈热毛巾不行吗?
Can't you just wrap a warm towel over my head?
要是闻到烧焦味 我会过来调低温度的
I'll lower the temperature if I smell anything singeing.
不如最开始就调为中度吧?
How about we start on medium?
我不用 最高温 谢谢
Not for me. Full blast, please.
Quinn
Quinn!
我做头发护理向来很耐高温之苦的
I have really high pain tolerance for hair-care treatments.
嘿 Trent 好消息
Hey, Trent, just so you know,
我们现在搞穿一送一活动呢
we're having a two-for-one special.
嘿 酷啊 Axl 这样一孔才11块
Hey, that's cool, Axl. 11 bucks each.
要来吗 Daria?
What do you say, Daria?
可以看看我们的穿孔菜单
Take a look at our piercing menu.
"小舌"应该不是这么写的吧?
I don't think that's how you spell "uvula."
那个不是"小舌"
That's not "uvula."
我一直想在这儿穿个孔
I've been wanting to put a hole right here.
永远不要往自己头上打太多孔
You can never have too many holes in your head.
来嘛 Daria 反正有特价
Come on, Daria. Let's get the special.
我可以打耳洞
I guess I could pierce my ears.
这个不行
Ah, no can do.
特价仅限单孔 耳洞是两个孔了
Special's one hole, ears are two holes.
只能原价买单
Full retail price applies.
而且那也太没新意了 Daria
That's too boring, anyway, Daria.
你得玩点有意思的
You gotta do something fun.
有意思?
Fun?
你来个唇孔会很漂亮
You'd look nice with a lip ring.
你就放任他这么打量我?
Are you going to let him talk to me that way?
我知道在哪儿穿孔会酷
I know what would be cool.
这儿放个小银环
Little silver hoop.
成 没问题 脐环享受特价
Yeah, okay. A navel ring works.
至少是个开始
It's a start, at least.
我才不要在肚脐上穿孔
I am not going to pierce my belly button.
肚脐又没得罪过我
It never did anything to me.
Daria 脐环真心很惹火的
Daria, it would look really hot.
嘿 你到18岁了 对吧?
Hey, you are 18, aren't you?
我应该先问的
I should've asked.
不到18岁有什么问题吗?
Is it a problem if I'm not?
是 你得拿到父母同意
Yeah. You'll need parental permission.
我们这行只允许向成人提供服务
This establishment is licensed to serve adults only
公司要严格遵照法律法规营业
and operates strictly according to the letter of the law.
- 她到了 - 行
- She is. - Right.
徒弟今天出门了
My apprentice is out today.
我得去看看是谁来了
I better go see who that is.
嘿 Axl 是我啦
Hey, Axl, it's just me.
好啊 亲爱的
Hello, darling.
Axl 我得再给鼻环这块拿点防腐剂用
Axl, I need some more of that antiseptic stuff for my nose ring.
Trent
Oh, Trent!
嘿 Monique 最近好吗?
Hey, Monique. How's it going?
很不错
Pretty good.
鹰女乐队怎么样?
How are the Harpies?
我在考虑单飞 这次是真的
I'm thinking of leaving, for real this time.
办我自己的乐队
Start my own band.
你行的 Monique
You could do it, Monique.
你舞台表现力一绝 正经的
You've got stage presence. No kidding.
我师从高人啊 老大
I learned from the best, man.
别扯了 Monique以前跟我在一个乐队
Aw, stop it. Monique used to be in a band with me.
嘿 Monique 这是Daria
Oh, hey, Monique, this is Daria.
我妹的朋友
My kid sister's friend.
嘿 Daria
Hey, Daria.
嗨
Hi.
Daria是我认识最酷的高中小孩
Daria's like the coolest high schooler I know.
卡仕曼购物中心
这件我穿会好看
That'll be good on me.
这件我穿肯定萌
That's cute for me.
我 我 我 我 我 这件可能给老妈 我 我
Me. Me. Me. Me. Me. Possible Mom. Me. Me.
Quinn 这身真心不好看啊
Quinn, this just isn't working.
Helen?
Eric
Eric!
这位是我侄女 Jasmine
This is Jasmine, my niece.
我带她来买生日礼物了
I'm buying her a birthday present.
嗨
Hi.
你好 Jasmine Quinn 这位是Eric叔叔 妈同事
Hello, Jasmine. Quinn, this is Eric, from work.
Eric Jasmine 这位是Quinn
And Eric, Jasmine, this is Quinn.
我会做她妈妈 她会做我女儿 去参加一场时装秀
She's going to be my daughter and I'm going to be her mother in a fashion show.
当然啦 她就是我亲闺女 我...
Actually, she is my daughter, and...
我只是想努力做一个好妈妈
I was just trying to be a good parent...
天啊 我都做了什么?
oh, my God, what have I done?
我喜欢那裙子 Eric叔
I like that skirt, Uncle Eric.
我是说 穿在我身上我比较喜欢
I mean... I'd like it on me.
我有说过我怕疼么?
Have I mentioned that I hate pain?
这个不疼的
Now, this won't hurt.
不会比挤痘痘疼的
It's no worse than popping a pimple.
我还什么都没做呢
I haven't done anything yet.
我在脑补挤痘痘有多疼
I was thinking about how much it hurts to pop a pimple.
你要是总发抖 我可就没法工作咯
I can't concentrate if you keep shaking.
我帮你渡过这关 Daria
I'll help you through this, Daria.
来
Here.
什么?
Uh... what's that?
这是我的手 把你的手给我
That's my hand. Give me yours.
很干净的 Daria
It's pretty clean, Daria.
不是啦 我... 抱歉
No, I, um... sorry.
现在最该做的事是 不要去想
The best thing to do is not think about it.
这样就不会疼了
Then it won't hurt.
真的不疼
It doesn't hurt.
什么?
What?
Daria?
六个月之内最好不要摘下这个环
Don't take out the ring for six months,
不然孔会闭合 我们就得重新打了
or it'll close up and we'll have to pierce it again.
如果流脓 不用太害怕
Don't get scared when the mucous starts pouring out.
往上面抹点这种防腐剂...
Put some of this antiseptic stuff on,
每天戴上50毫克重的金属环或者...
and take 50 milligrams a day of um, some metal or other...
镀锌还是铝环 我忘了
zinc, aluminum, I forget.
你弄完了?
You did it?
我穿孔了?
I'm pierced?
不要啊 马桶又跟我说话了
Oh, no. The toilet is talking to me again.
Lane
Lane!
会说话的马桶 你应该叫我Jane
Talking toilet, you may call me "Jane."
是你啊
Oh! It's you.
你看到的是真的吗?
Did I just see what I think I saw?
你不会看到一个啜泣贞女什么的吧 有吗?
You didn't see a weeping virgin or anything, did you?
再看一眼
Do that again.
没想到你还蛮有种啊
I can't believe you had the nerve.
我也没想到 是Trent的主意
Neither can I. It was Trent's idea.
看来你真和Trent逛街去了
So you did go out with Trent.
给你买生日礼物去了... 呃
Shopping for your birthday present... oops.
他想给你惊喜来着
He wanted to surprise you.
然后他就在你肚脐儿送我一个孔
And he go me a hole in your navel.
好好惊喜噢
That is a surprise.
我也不知道怎么回事
I don't know how it happened,
我们俩在一块 他带我进店
but there we were and there he was,
店里正好在搞穿一赠一特价
and there was this two-for-one special...
天啊 我做了什么啊?
oh, my God, what have I done?
哎呀呀 我们的小女生变成女人咯
Oh, dear, our little girl's becoming a woman.
闭嘴
Shut up.
还不懂嘛 Daria
Don't you get it, Daria?
你为一男生做了这种蠢事
You did something stupid for a guy.
天啊 你终于也可以入乡随俗了
Gee, you may join the human race after all.
我才不是为了谁做的
I didn't do it for a guy.
我做是为了Trent能拿到特价
I did it so Trent could get the special.
有什么不同么
Oh, that's different.
嘿 你俩最后给我买啥了?
Hey, what'd you end up getting me?
不能说
I can't say.
希望是美术工具
I hope it's art tools.
我工具不够用了
I need some new supplies.
我确实是为男生穿孔的 对不?
I did do it for a guy, didn't I?
肯定的
Oh, yeah.
痒死了 我再也不会给任何人看了
It itches like hell, and I'm not showing anybody else.
把衬衫揶腰带里 没人会知道的
Just keep your shirt tucked in. No one will know.
嘿 Jodie 快来围观Daria的脐环
Hey, Jodie, check out Daria's navel ring.
真的 还蛮酷的诶
Really? That's kind of cool.
有吗?
It is?
有啊 只要你不是为了男生才去穿的孔
Yeah. As long as you didn't just do it for some guy.
是啊 为男生就俗了
Right. That would be bad.
你不会真做了吧
You didn't really do that!
做什么?
Do what?
那个
That!
这破东西啊?
Oh, this old thing?
只有戴上它 我才能忘掉自己的肚脐多难看
I only wear it when I don't care how my navel looks.
我懂了啦
Mmm... I get it.
想拿这种小玩意儿点缀自己的无聊人生对吧?
You're trying to brighten your ho-hum life with a little illusion.
我见过这种假脐环的 Daria
I've seen those fake rings, Daria.
我也见过 假的来不了这个
So have I. They don't do this.
也不会把人搞得这么痒
They don't itch like this, either.
老爸老妈会抓狂到疯的
Mom and Dad are gonna freak!
你觉得在你大赛前夜惹毛老爸老妈
Do you think you should be upsetting mom or dad
真的会很好嘛?
on the eve of your big competition?
这事儿是咱俩的小秘密 亲
It'll just be our little secret... sis.
你可能是时尚的一小步 却是瘙痒的一大步
You may be fashion forward but you itch like hell.
你来干嘛? 一个小时后才上学呢
What are you doing here? School's not for an hour.
没了
It's gone.
什么没了?
What's gone?
我穿孔没了 闭合了
I'm not pierced anymore. It closed up.
你不会把环取出来了吧?
You didn't take the ring out?
就一晚而已 痒得我受不了了
Just for the night. I couldn't stand the itching.
我听说过快速治疗 但你这也太扯了
I've heard of fast healers but this is ridiculous.
天啊 没准外星人ET进我物屋子 趁我睡觉摸了我肚脐
Gee, maybe E.T. came in my room and touched my navel while I slept.
天 Daria 你做梦真是无敌诡异
Boy, Daria, you have the weirdest dreams.
别告诉Trent
Don't tell Trent.
ET的事吗?
About E.T.?
肚脐的事
About my belly button.
关他毛事啊?
What does he care?
反正他行了你别说就是了 好吧?
Just don't say anything when he wakes up, okay?
他一两个小时醒不了 一两天都说不定
That won't happen for hours. Maybe days.
嘿 Daria
Hey, Daria.
Trent?
玩排练?
Late rehearsal?
或者早排练 随便了
Or early. Whatever.
你穿孔闭合了是么?
So your piercing closed up?
怪我不小心
It was an accident.
是啊 这事儿很常见
Yeah, that happens a lot.
你不会因为这事儿就变成怪咖 对吧?
And it doesn't make you a geek. Right?
当然不会
Of course not.
这样吧 等你准备好
Tell you what. When you're ready,
我们进城去纹身 纹身永远不会消失
we'll go down and get you a tattoo. They last forever.
我喜欢Tiffany 真心的
I love Tiffany, I really do.
她太悲剧了
She's so smushy.
不过她妈妈怎么感觉... 怪怪的?
But isn't there something a little strange about her... mother?
她跟代理公司说她想要最漂亮的模特
She told the agency she wanted the prettiest model they had.
其实也还好啦
I guess it's okay.
你看Brittany
I mean, look at Brittany.
我们应该设立一条继母的规则
There should've been a rule about stepmothers.
Quinn? 该我们咯
Quinn? We're next.
记住 老妈 一心向萌
Remember, Mom, think cute.
最新 挺胸 太...
Confident, up, totally...
太丢人了
Totally humiliating.
你还没告诉我Trent到底要送我什么礼物呢
You still haven't told me what present Trent came up with.
耐心点 答案终将揭晓
Be patient. All will be revealed.
各位好 我们是七彩玄乐队 我想对我妹妹Jane说句生日快乐
Hello. We're Mystik Spiral and I want to say happy birthday to my sister, Jane.
这首歌献给你 Jane
This for you, Jane.
♪ 小妹小妹 你像龙卷风闯进我生活 ♪
♪ Little sister, little sister you came into my life like a twister. ♪
♪ 还能给你什么你尚未夺走的东东? ♪
♪ What can I get you that you haven't taken? ♪
♪ 还能给你什么没被贪婪吞噬的东东? ♪
♪ What can I get you that hasn't been killed by corruption and greed? ♪
♪ 还能给你什么东东? 没扎染或你还没拥有 ♪
♪ What can I get you that isn't tie-dyed or like what you already have, ♪
♪ 塑料或死物 或悲伤如我 ♪
♪ or plastic or not alive or so sad? ♪
♪ 谁人知道 ♪
♪ Does anybody know, ♪
♪ 谁人知道我们为何活着? ♪
♪ does anybody know why we're here? ♪
♪ 谁人知道 ♪
♪ Does anybody know, ♪
♪ 谁人知道我们为何活着? ♪
♪ does anybody know why we're here? ♪
♪ 谁人知道 ♪
♪ Does anybody know, ♪
♪ 谁人知道我们为何活着? ♪
♪ does anybody know why we're here? ♪
顺便 谢谢你送的超酷美术工具
By the way, thanks for the cool art supplies.
总得有人送不是
Somebody had to do it.
付出那么多 准备那么久 为什么是我出糗 为什么?
All that work. All that preparation. Why? Why me?
亲爱的 这次只是个小小的校园筹款会嘛
Honey, it was just a little school fund-raiser.
你大放光彩的机会还多着呢
You'll have other moments in the sun.
但都不是和你了 老妈
But none with you, Mom.
诶哟 好好贴心哦
Oh, that's so sweet.
不是那个意思 是禁用你 禁走怪咖风
Nope. None with you. No freaking way.
Quinn 做什么事能让你心情好一点吗?
Quinn, isn't there anything that would make you feel better?
有的 有的有的
Yes! Yes, there is.
我们要看看你的脐环 年轻人
We want to see your belly button, young lady,
现在就要看
and we want to see it now.
你在说什么啊?
What are you talking about?
快露出来
Out with it!
对我肚脐有什么意见吗?
Do you have a problem with innies?
Quinn 你怎么回事啊?
Quinn, what's the matter with you?
你姐根本没穿孔
Your sister's not pierced.
干嘛要这样吓唬我们?
Why would you scare us like that?
可... 可昨天我还看见来着
But... but it was there yesterday!
拿那种小玩意儿点缀自己的无聊人生吗?
Trying to brighten your ho-hum life with a little illusion?
哎 我困了 晚安 各位
Boy, I'm tired. Night, everybody.
她穿过孔 穿过的 不骗你们
She was pierced... pierced, I tell you!
人性啊...
Oh, the humanity...
欢迎微博关注
@漫迪字幕组